Guide to the Committee of 100 on the Federal City records [Part II], 1909-1996 MS2131
Special Collections Research Center, The George Washington University
- Subcommittee files, 1967-1996; MS2131 Series 2; 7.5 Linear feet (Box 9, Box 10, Box 22, Box 23, Box 19, Box 18, Box 21, Box 20, Box 16, Box 15, Box 17, Box 12, Box 11, Box 14, Box 13)
  - Historic Preservation: Correspondence, from the chairman of the Historic Preservation subcommittee re:preservation of the Eastern Market, 1994 (Box 9, Folder 4)
  - Historic Preservation: Subjects/Issues Files, related to Archibold Cabin preservation issue, 1992 (Box 9, Folder 5)
  - Historic Preservation: Subjects/Issues Files, related to the Archibold-Glover Parkway, 1991 (Box 9, Folder 6)
  - Historic Preservation: Subjects/Issues Files, related to the Barney House preservation issue, 1992-1994 (Box 9, Folder 7)
  - Historic Preservation: Subjects/Issues Files, related to the Carter Barron Land swap preservation issue, 1992 (Box 9, Folder 8)
  - Historic Preservation: Subjects/Issues Files, related to the Church of Christ Science building preservation issue, 1990-1992 (Box 9, Folder 9)
  - Historic Preservation: Subjects/Issues Files, related to the Cleveland Park Historic District preservation issue, 1983-1986 (Box 9, Folder 10)
  - Historic Preservation: Subjects/Issues Files, related to the Cleveland Park - Park and Shop preservation issue, 1988-1991 (Box 9, Folder 11)
  - Historic Preservation: Subjects/Issues Files, related to the subject of Clyde' Barge, 1989 (Box 9, Folder 12)
  - Historic Preservation: Subjects/Issues Files, related to the preservation of the building at 3901 Connecticut Avenue, 1996 (Box 10, Folder 1)
  - Historic Preservation: Subjects/Issues Files, Clippings and notes related to the Corcoran Gallery, 1995 ca. (Box 10, Folder 2)
  - Historic Preservation: Subjects/Issues Files, related to the preservation of the Hecht Company building, 1991 (Box 10, Folder 3)
  - Historic Preservation: Subjects/Issues Files, related to the preservation of the Hurt home, 1991 (Box 10, Folder 4)
  - Historic Preservation: Subjects/Issues Files, related to the subject of the McMillan Park Reservoir, 1990-1991 (Box 10, Folder 5)
  - Historic Preservation: Subjects/Issues Files, related to the subject of the proposed demolition of a historic building at the Washington D.C. Navy Yard, 1992 (Box 10, Folder 6)
  - Historic Preservation: Subjects/Issues Files, related to the issue of 499 New Jersey Avenue, 1995-1996 (Box 10, Folder 7)
  - Historic Preservation: Subjects/Issues Files, related to the preservation of 2501 Pennsylvania Avenue, 1991 (Box 10, Folder 8)
  - Historic Preservation: Subjects/Issues Files, related to the issue of the Sears Building, 1995 (Box 10, Folder 9)
  - Historic Preservation: Subjects/Issues Files, Clippings and Correspondence related to the Senator Theatre, 1990-1991 (Box 10, Folder 10)
  - Historic Preservation: Subjects/Issues Files, Correspondence and a news clipping regarding preservation of the Tivoli Theatre, 1989 (Box 10, Folder 11)
  - Historic Preservation: Subjects/Issues Files, Press Release from the Historical Society of Washington D.C. re: Historical Society Awards Preservation Prize to two Committee members for their work towards preserving the Woodie's Warehouse, 1991 (Box 10, Folder 12)
  - Historic Preservation: Subjects/Issues Files, related to the Victor Building, 1992-1994 (Box 10, Folder 13)
  - Housing: Subjects/Issues Files, "Capital for D.C. Housing" files, 1990 (Box 11, Folder 1)
  - Housing: Subjects/Issues Files, relating to the Housing Production Act, 1993 (Box 11, Folder 2)
  - Membership: Meetings Files, minutes of and other files collected from the meetings of the Membership Subcommittee, 1967 (Box 12, Folder 1)
  - Membership: Meetings Files, minutes of and other files collected from the meetings of the Membership Subcommittee, 1975 (Box 12, Folder 2)
  - Membership: Meetings Files, minutes of and other files collected from the meetings of the Membership Subcommittee, 1976 (Box 12, Folder 3)
  - Membership: Meetings Files, minutes of and other files collected from the meetings of the Membership Subcommittee, 1977 (Box 12, Folder 4)
  - Membership: Meetings Files, minutes of and other files collected from the meetings of the Membership Subcommittee, 1978 (Box 12, Folder 5)
  - Membership: Meetings Files, minutes of and other files collected from the meetings of the Membership Subcommittee including correspondence and reports, 1979 (Box 12, Folder 6)
  - Membership: Meetings Files, minutes of and other files collected from the meetings of the Membership Subcommittee, 1980 (Box 12, Folder 7)
  - Membership: Meetings Files, minutes of the meetings of the Membership Subcommittee, 1981 (Box 12, Folder 8)
  - Membership: Meetings Files, minutes of and other files collected from the meetings of the Membership Subcommittee, 1982 (Box 12, Folder 9)
  - Membership: Meetings Files, minutes of and other files collected from the meetings of the Membership Subcommittee, 1983 (Box 12, Folder 10)
  - Membership: Meetings Files, minutes of and other files collected from the meetings of the Membership Subcommittee, 1984 (Box 12, Folder 11)
  - Membership: Meetings Files, minutes of and other files collected from the meetings of the Membership Subcommittee, 1985 (Box 12, Folder 12)
  - Membership: Meetings Files, minutes of and other files collected from the meetings of the Membership Subcommittee, 1986 (Box 12, Folder 13)
  - Membership: Meetings Files, minutes of and other files collected from the meetings of the Membership Subcommittee, 1987 (Box 12, Folder 14)
  - Membership: Meetings Files, minutes of and other files collected from the meetings of the Membership Subcommittee, 1988 (Box 12, Folder 15)
  - Membership: Meetings Files, minutes of and other files collected from the meetings of the Membership Subcommittee, 1989 (Box 12, Folder 16)
  - Membership: Meetings Files, minutes of and other files collected from the meetings of the Membership Subcommittee, 1990 (Box 12, Folder 17)
  - Membership: Meetings Files, minutes of and other files collected from the meetings of the Membership Subcommittee, 1991 (Box 12, Folder 18)
  - Membership: Meetings Files, minutes of and other files collected from the meetings of the Membership Subcommittee, 1992 (Box 12, Folder 19)
  - Membership: Meetings Files, minutes of and other files collected from the meetings of the Membership Subcommittee, 1993 (Box 12, Folder 20)
  - Membership: Meetings Files, minutes of and other files collected from the meetings of the Membership Subcommittee, 1994 (Box 12, Folder 21)
  - Membership: Meetings Files, minutes of and other files, including some from the trustees meetings and a list of all members, collected from the meetings of the Membership Subcommittee, 1995 (Box 13, Folder 1)
  - Membership: Meetings Files, minutes of and other files, including a list of all members, collected from the meetings of the Membership Subcommittee, 1996 (Box 13, Folder 2)
  - Membership: Dues Renewal Notices, cards, notices and envelopes related to dues renewal, 1990 ca.-1996 (Box 13, Folder 3)
  - Parks and Conservation: Subjects/Issues Files, Correspondence and Clippings related to Capital Crescent Park, 1987-1993 (Box 14, Folder 1)
  - Parks and Conservation: Subjects/Issues Files, Correspondence and Clippings related to the Mall Park System, 1994 (Box 14, Folder 2)
  - Parks and Conservation: Subjects/Issues Files, Miscellaneous documents related to the Walt Whitman Park, undated (Box 14, Folder 3)
  - Planning and Urban Design: Subjects/Issues Files, Clippings and a request for proposal on the Anacostia River West Bank Development Program, 1987 (Box 15, Folder 1)
  - Planning and Urban Design: Subjects/Issues Files, Clippings and correspondence about Casino Proposals, 1993 (Box 15, Folder 2)
  - Planning and Urban Design: Subjects/Issues Files, development agreement between Children's Island and Developer, 1983 (Box 15, Folder 3)
  - Planning and Urban Design: Subjects/Issues Files, documents papers, presentations, clippings and correspondence from the Clean Air Task Force, 1988-1992 (Box 15, Folder 4)
  - Planning and Urban Design: Subjects/Issues Files, documents papers, presentations, clippings and correspondence from the Clean Air Task Force, 1992-1993 (Box 15, Folder 5)
  - Planning and Urban Design: Subjects/Issues Files, correspondence and clippings about the proposed DisneyAmerica theme park, 1993-1994 (Box 15, Folder 6)
  - Planning and Urban Design: Subjects/Issues Files, documents related to the Department of Transportation Headquarters building, 1990 ca. (Box 15, Folder 7)
  - Planning and Urban Design: Subjects/Issues Files, correspondence, clippings and statements related to the Downtown Development district, 1989-1991 (Box 15, Folder 8)
  - Planning and Urban Design: Subjects/Issues Files, correspondence, clippings and reports related to the Downtown Development district, 1990-1992 (Box 15, Folder 9)
  - Planning and Urban Design: Subjects/Issues Files, correspondence, clippings and reports related to the Downtown Development district, 1990-1993 (Box 15, Folder 10)
  - Planning and Urban Design: Subjects/Issues Files, documents related to Engine Company 24, 1993 (Box 15, Folder 11)
  - Planning and Urban Design: Subjects/Issues Files, correspondence and report about General Services Administration heating plants, 1992-1993 (Box 15, Folder 12)
  - Planning and Urban Design: Subjects/Issues Files, clippings and other files related to the development of Greathouse Tract, 1992 (Box 15, Folder 13)
  - Planning and Urban Design: Subjects/Issues Files, related to planning and the Metro garage site, 1993 (Box 16, Folder 1)
  - Planning and Urban Design: Subjects/Issues Files, related to planning and the Municipal Fish Wharf, 1992-1993 (Box 16, Folder 2)
  - Planning and Urban Design: Subjects/Issues Files, related to planning and the National Building Museum, 1990-1992 (Box 16, Folder 3)
  - Planning and Urban Design: Subjects/Issues Files, related to planning and PortAmerica, 1988-1994 (Box 16, Folder 4)
  - Planning and Urban Design: Subjects/Issues Files, related to planning and the Redskins Stadium Land Transfer, 1985-1986 (Box 16, Folder 5)
  - Planning and Urban Design: Subjects/Issues Files, related to planning and the Redskins Stadium rehabilitation of RFK, 1993 (Box 16, Folder 6)
  - Planning and Urban Design: Subjects/Issues Files, related to planning and the Redskins Stadium economic impact study, 1991-1993 (Box 16, Folder 7)
  - Planning and Urban Design: Subjects/Issues Files, related to planning and the Redskins Stadium congressional testimony, 1993 (Box 16, Folder 8)
  - Planning and Urban Design: Subjects/Issues Files, related to planning and the Redskins Stadium special reference, 1993 (Box 16, Folder 9)
  - Planning and Urban Design: Subjects/Issues Files, related to planning and the Silver Spring Mega Mall project, 1995 (Box 16, Folder 10)
  - Planning and Urban Design: Subjects/Issues Files, related to planning and the Southeast Federal Center, 1992 (Box 16, Folder 11)
  - Planning and Urban Design: Subjects/Issues Files, related to planning and the Ward 5 plans, 1993 (Box 16, Folder 12)
  - Planning and Urban Design: Subjects/Issues Files, related to planning and Woodie's Warehouse, 1993 (Box 16, Folder 13)
  - Planning and Urban Design: Subjects/Issues Files, related to planning and the Woodland-Normanstone Subdivision, 1989-1990 (Box 16, Folder 14)
  - Transportation: Statements, of Edward Lyle, the chairman of the Transportation subcommittee, before the U.S. Senate, 1984 (Box 17, Folder 1)
  - Transportation: Meetings Files, of the March 3rd meeting of the Transportation subcommittee, 1988 (Box 17, Folder 2)
  - Transportation: Correspondence, related to the issues of the Transportation subcommittee, 1982-1984 (Box 17, Folder 3)
  - Transportation: Subjects Files, related to Airports, 1980-1981 (Box 17, Folder 4)
  - Transportation: Subjects Files, related to Airports, 1980-1984 (Box 17, Folder 5)
  - Transportation: Subjects Files, correspondence, clippings and other files related to the Barney Circle road project, 1983-1988 (Box 17, Folder 6)
  - Transportation: Subjects Files, correspondence, clippings and other files related to the Barney Circle road project, 1984-1988 (Box 17, Folder 7)
  - Transportation: Subjects Files, correspondence, clippings and other files related to the Barney Circle road project, 1988-1993 (Box 17, Folder 8)
  - Transportation: Subjects Files, correspondence, clippings and other files related to the Barney Circle road project, 1992-1993 (Box 17, Folder 9)
  - Transportation: Subjects Files, correspondence, clippings and other files related to the Barney Circle road project, 1993 (Box 17, Folder 10)
  - Transportation: Subjects Files, correspondence, clippings and other files related to the Beach Drive road project, 1980-1994 (Box 18, Folder 11)
  - Transportation: Subjects Files, correspondence, clippings and other files related to Board of Trade Initiatives, 1980-1984 (Box 18, Folder 12)
  - Transportation: Subjects Files, correspondence, clippings and other files related to the CSX Georgetown Spur, 1986-1989 (Box 18, Folder 13)
  - Transportation: Subjects Files, correspondence, clippings and other files related to long range transportation planning, 1991-1993 (Box 18, Folder 14)
  - Transportation: Subjects Files, correspondence, clippings and other files related to Metro financing, 1981-1984 (Box 18, Folder 15)
  - Transportation: Subjects Files, correspondence, clippings and other files related to Metro financing, 1982-1984 (Box 18, Folder 16)
  - Transportation: Subjects Files, correspondence, clippings and other files related to the Metro Green Line, 1982-1984 (Box 18, Folder 17)
  - Transportation: Subjects Files, reports on Metro and Transportation Improvement Programs, 1987-1992 (Box 18, Folder 18)
  - Transportation: Subjects Files, correspondence, clippings and other files related to the issues of Interstate 66 and George Washington Parkway, 1981-1983 (Box 18, Folder 19)
  - Transportation: Subjects Files, correspondence, clippings and other files related to the Northern Virginia Transportation Commission, 1986 (Box 18, Folder 20)
  - Transportation: Subjects Files, correspondence, clippings and other files dealing with regionalplanning, 1991-1992 (Box 18, Folder 21)
  - Transportation: Subjects Files, correspondence, clippings and other files dealing with regional planning, 1992 (Box 18, Folder 22)
  - Transportation: Subjects Files, correspondence, clippings, reports and other files dealing with the Regional Planning Alternative project, 1992 (Box 19, Folder 1)
  - Transportation: Subjects Files, Press Kit, reports and correspondence dealing with the Reno Road project, 1980-1982 (Box 19, Folder 2)
  - Transportation: Subjects Files, Reports and other files related to the Transportation Improvement Program project, 1991 (Box 19, Folder 3)
  - Transportation: Subjects Files, clippings, correspondence and other files related to transportation management and clean air, 1991-1994 (Box 19, Folder 4)
  - Transportation: Subject Files, related to the Washington By-pass project, 1990 (Box 20, Folder 1)
  - Transportation: Subject Files, related to the Washington By-pass project, 1990 (Box 20, Folder 2)
  - Transportation: Subject Files, related to the Washington By-pass project, 1990 (Box 20, Folder 3)
  - Transportation: Subject Files, related to the Wisconsin Avenue Corridor, 1986-1987 (Box 20, Folder 4)
  - Transportation: Subject Files, related to the Wisconsin Avenue Corridor, 1986-1987 (Box 20, Folder 5)
  - Transportation: Subject Files, related to the Woodrow Wilson Bridge issues and projects, 1986-1991 (Box 20, Folder 6)
  - Water Resources: Subject Files, related to Woodrow Wilson Bridge widening project, 1991 (Box 21, Folder 1)
  - Water Resources: Subjects Files, related to the "Union Station Transportation Management Taxing District Act,", 1990 (Box 21, Folder 2)
  - Water Resources: Subjects Files, related to issues surrounding the Blue Plains Treatment Plant, 1994 (Box 21, Folder 3)
  - Zoning: Subjects Files, Correspondence, clippings and files related to the Blagden Alley issue, 1990-1995 (Box 22, Folder 1)
  - Zoning: Subjects Files, Correspondence, clippings and files related to the Buzzard Point issue, 1989 (Box 22, Folder 2)
  - Zoning: Subjects Files, Correspondence, clippings and files related to the Capital Point Project, 1988 (Box 22, Folder 3)
  - Zoning: Subjects Files, Correspondence, clippings and files related to the Center Leg Freeway Air Rights issue, 1989 (Box 22, Folder 4)
  - Zoning: Subjects Files, related to the D.C. Prison Site issue, 1986-1987 (Box 22, Folder 5)
  - Zoning: Subjects Files, related to the D.C. Prison Site issue, 1986-1987 (Box 22, Folder 6)
  - Zoning: Subjects Files, related to the Eastern Market issue, 1991 (Box 22, Folder 7)
  - Zoning: Subjects Files, related to the Federal Triangle issue, 1991 (Box 22, Folder 8)
  - Zoning: Subjects Files, related to the Re-Zoning of Foggy Bottom issue, 1991 (Box 22, Folder 9)
  - Zoning: Subjects Files, clippings and correspondence related to the Georgetown Co-Generator issue, 1991-1993 (Box 22, Folder 10)
  - Zoning: Subjects Files, related to the Harrison Institute Study to determine the D.C. City Council's authority in relation to the Comprehensive Plan, 1986-1988 (Box 22, Folder 11)
  - Zoning: Subjects Files, notes and correspondence related to the Zoning Initiative 17, 1990 (Box 22, Folder 12)
  - Zoning: Subjects Files, Correspondence and files related to the zoning issues at 1003 Kearney Street, NE, 1991 (Box 22, Folder 13)
  - Zoning: Subjects Files, Correspondence and files related to the zoning issues in Market Square North, 1991 (Box 23, Folder 1)
  - Zoning: Subjects Files, Correspondence and files related to the zoning issues in Mason Neck, 1990 (Box 23, Folder 2)
  - Zoning: Subjects Files, Correspondence, clippings and files related to zoning issues and the NBC-WRC tower, 1992 (Box 23, Folder 3)
  - Zoning: Subjects Files, Correspondence, clippings and files related to zoning issues and the NBC-WRC tower, 1992 (Box 23, Folder 4)
  - Zoning: Subjects Files, Correspondence and clippings related to the Shaw neighborhood, 1989 (Box 23, Folder 5)
  - Zoning: Subjects Files, a message from the Shepherd Park Legal Defense Fund Committee, 1985 (Box 23, Folder 6)
  - Zoning: Subjects Files, correspondence, clippings and other files related to zoning issues and small buildings in downtown D.C., 1988-1989 (Box 23, Folder 7)
  - Zoning: Subjects Files, correspondence and statements about the Spring Valley West zoning issues, 1993-1994 (Box 23, Folder 8)
  - Zoning: Subjects Files, related to projects and zoning issues related to Station Place, 1990 (Box 23, Folder 9)
  - Zoning: Subjects Files, Clippings and other files related to zoning issues surrounding the U.S. International, Cultural and Trade Center project developments in Federal Triangle, 1987-1992 (Box 23, Folder 10)
  - Zoning: Subjects Files, Correspondence, clippings and other files related to the Western Presbyterian Church move to a Virginia suburb and zoning issues related to the International Monetary Fund building expansion, 1991-1995 (Box 23, Folder 11)
  - Zoning: Subjects Files, Reports, correspondence and other files related to the zoning issues related to the WETA tower and the George Washington University, 1993 (Box 23, Folder 12)
  - Zoning: Subjects Files, Reports, correspondence and other files related to the zoning issues related to the WETA tower and the George Washington University, 1993-1994 (Box 23, Folder 13)